Guide to the Leonard Jimmie Savage Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1946-1972; Series I; 15 linear feet (34 boxes)
  - Kuh, Edwin (2), 1956 (Box 19, Folder 468)
  - Kullback, Solomon (1), 1963 (Box 66B, Folder 67)
  - Kyburg, Henry E., Jr. (30), 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 469)
  - Kyburg, Henry E., Jr. (26), 1963-1966, 1968-1970 (Box 19, Folder 470)
  - Kyburg, Henry E., Jr. (4), 1964-1965, 1967 (Box 66B, Folder 68)
  - L (33), 1946-1947, 1955, 1959-1967, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 471)
  - Lai, Son Lin (2), 1969 (Box 66B, Folder 69)
  - Lakatos, Imre (3), 1969 (Box 20, Folder 472)
  - Landau, Emanuel, undated
  - Latane, Henry Allan (18), 1957-1960, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 473)
  - Laurent, André Gilbert Louis (33), 1956-1957, 1961-1964 (Box 20, Folder 474)
  - Laurent, André Gilbert Louis (5), 1957, 1961 (Box 66B, Folder 70)
  - Lazarowitz, Alice A. (4), 1966 (Box 20, Folder 475)
  - Lazarsfeld, Paul Felix (3), 1959 (Box 20, Folder 476)
  - Leamer, Edward E. (3), 1971 (Box 20, Folder 477)
  - Le Cam, Lucien Marie (8), 1953, 1962, 1964, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 478)
  - Lehmann, Erich Leo (12), 1948, 1950-1953 (Box 20, Folder 479)
  - Lehmann, Erich Leo (27), 1954-1955, 1959-1962, 1964, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 480)
  - Lehmann, Erich Leo (2), 1952, undated (Box 66B, Folder 71)
  - Leipnik, Roy Bergh (3), 1959-1960 (Box 20, Folder 481)
  - Leipnik, Roy Bergh (2), 1966 (Box 66B, Folder 71)
  - Levi, Isaac (4), 1964, 1966 (Box 66B, Folder 71)
  - Levy, Paul (13), 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 481)
  - Lew, Edward A. (5), 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 482)
  - Leyvraz, J. P. (5), 1967 (Box 20, Folder 482)
  - Lieberstein, H. M. (3), 1962 (Box 20, Folder 483)
  - Lindley, Dennis Victor (24), 1952-1953, 1955-1956, 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 484)
  - Lindley, Dennis Victor (34), 1960-1964, 1966, 1968-1969, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 485)
  - Lindley, Dennis Victor (5), 1953, 1967 (Box 66B, Folder 72)
  - Lindsay, Robert G. (1), 1959 (Box 20, Folder 486)
  - Ling, Robert F. (6), 1966, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 487)
  - Ling, Robert F. (8), 1971 (Box 20, Folder 488)
  - Ling, Robert F. (1), 1969 (Box 66B, Folder 73)
  - "The List" (20), 1967-1971 (Box 20, Folder 489)
  - Litwin, Samuel (2), 1965 (Box 20, Folder 490)
  - Loeve, M. (7), 1950-1951 (Box 20, Folder 490)
  - Lorie, James H. (27), 1955, 1957, 1959, 1961, 1964-1968, 1970, n. d. (Box 20, Folder 491)
  - Lowe, Marian (9), 1959, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 492)
  - Lubin, Ardie (2), 1953 (Box 20, Folder 492)
  - Luce, R. Duncan (14), 1955 (Box 20, Folder 493)
  - Luce, R. Duncan (13), 1960-1961, 1967, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 494)
  - Lukacs, Eugene (3), 1954, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 495)
  - Lund, Iver A. (4), 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 495)
  - Lundegard, Robert James (35), 1961-1965 (Box 20, Folder 496)
  - Lundegard, Robert James (1), 1964 (Box 66B, Folder 73)
  - Lusted, Lee Browning (8), 1966, 1968, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 497)
  - M (48), 1942, 1945, 1957-1958, 1960-1971 (Box 21, Folder 498)
  - McCarthy, John (4), 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 499)
  - McCulloch, Warren S. (5), 1948, 1953, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 499)
  - McCutcheon, Terry (1), 1969 (Box 21, Folder 500)
  - MacDonald, Verne H. (9), 1968, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 501)
  - MacDonald, Verne H. (1), 1970 (Box 66B, Folder 74)
  - McGee, Victor e. (1), 1968 (Box 66B, Folder 74)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, Inc. (3), 1948 (Box 21, Folder 502)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, Inc. (26), 1960-1962 (Box 21, Folder 503)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, Inc. (24), 1963 (Box 21, Folder 504)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, Inc. (26), 1964 (Box 21, Folder 505)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, Inc. (30), 1965-1966, 1968, 1972, undated (Box 21, Folder 506)
  - Machol, Robert Engel (26), 1960-1965 (Box 21, Folder 507)
  - Machol, Robert Engel (30), 1966 (Box 21, Folder 508)
  - Machol, Robert Engel (25), 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 509)
  - Machol, Robert Engel (40), 1969-1971 (Box 21, Folder 510)
  - Machol, Robert Engel (4), 1964, 1967, 1970 (Box 66B, Folder 75)
  - MacLane, Saunders (3), 1946, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 511)
  - The Macmillan Company (1), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 511)
  - MacQueen, James B. (3), 1962 (Box 21, Folder 511)
  - McQueen, James B. (6), 1961-1962 (Box 66B, Folder 76)
  - Madansky, Albert (9), 1957-1960, 1962, undated (Box 21, Folder 512)
  - Madansky, Albert (10), 1962 (Box 66B, Folder 77)
  - Maddala, G. S. (3), 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 513)
  - Madow, William G. (8), 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 514)
  - Mahalanobis, P. C. (10), 1958 (Box 21, Folder 515)
  - Maitra, Anis Kumar (4), 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 516)
  - Majone, Giandomenico (10), 1959, 1963, 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 516)
  - Majone, Giandomenico (4), 1968 (Box 66B, Folder 78)
  - Malinvaud, E. (7), 1955, 1959-1960, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 517)
  - Maloney, Clifford Joseph (10), 1969-1971 (Box 22, Folder 518)
  - Maltenfort, George Gunther (4), 1960 (Box 22, Folder 519)
  - Mandelbrot, Benoit (30), 1953-1954, 1955-1956, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 520)
  - Mandelbrot, Benoit (13), 1961, 1963, 1965, 1967-1969, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 521)
  - Mandelbrot, Benoit (5), 1959, 1962, 1968-1969 (Box 66B, Folder 79)
  - Mann, Henry B. (3), 1960 (Box 22, Folder 522)
  - Manos, Nicholas Emmanuel (19), 1957-1958, undated (Box 22, Folder 523)
  - Mansfield, Edwin (1), 1957 (Box 22, Folder 524)
  - Manz, Bruno Julius (1), 1970 (Box 22, Folder 525)
  - Marangoni, Corinna (11), 1960-1961, 1963-1964, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 526)
  - Margolin, Myron H. (3), 1971 (Box 22, Folder 527)
  - Markowitz, Harry (2), 1953, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 527)
  - Marschak, Jacob (25), 1952, 1956, 1962-1963 1965-1966, 1969, 1971, undated (Box 22, Folder 528)
  - Marshall, Andrew W. (2), 1965 (Box 22, Folder 529)
  - Martin, Margaret Pearl (6), 1957-1959 (Box 22, Folder 529)
  - Martin, Margaret Pearl (8), 1957, 1959, 1966-1968 (Box 66B, Folder 80)
  - Martinez, Luis de la Campa (3), 1961, 1964, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 530)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Radiation Laboratory (1), 1943 (Box 22, Folder 531)
  - Massé, P. (2), 1954 (Box 22, Folder 531)
  - Massey, G. Eric (4), 1958 (Box 66B, Folder 81)
  - Mathematical Reviews (33), 1950, 1951, 1953-1954, 1956, 1958-1961, 1966-1967, 1969-1971 (Box 22, Folder 532)
  - Mathematics Research Center (2), 1962 (Box 22, Folder 533)
  - The Mathematics Teacher (2), 1967 (Box 22, Folder 533)
  - Maule, Harper Jaanz (1), 1955 (Box 22, Folder 534)
  - May, Kenneth Ownsworth (3), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 535)
  - Mayerson, Allen L. (11), 1962-1964 (Box 22, Folder 535)
  - Meier, Paul (4), 1959-1960, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 536)
  - G. and C. Merriam Company (9), 1969 (Box 22, Folder 537)
  - Merton, Robert K. (2), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 538)
  - Metron (3), 1959, 1961, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 538)
  - Meyer, Herman (3), 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 538)
  - Michigan State University (3), 1960, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 539)
  - Michigan, University of (2), 1940-1941 (Box 22, Folder 540)
  - Michigan, University of (22), 1960-1964 (Box 22, Folder 541)
  - Michigan, University of, Department of Mathematics (10), 1963-1964 (Box 22, Folder 542)
  - Michigan, University of, School of Public Health (1), 1970 (Box 22, Folder 543)
  - Michigan, University of, School of Public Health (2), 1970 (Box 66B, Folder 81)
  - Miller, James Grier (3), 1962 (Box 22, Folder 544)
  - Milliken, William Grawn (1), 1971 (Box 22, Folder 545)
  - Minton, Paul Dixon (2), 1967 (Box 22, Folder 545)
  - Mirkil, Hazleton (4), 1960 (Box 22, Folder 546)
  - Mitter, Oniel Kumar (9), 1967-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 547)
  - Mitter, Oniel Kumar (47), 1967-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 66B, Folder 82)
  - Miyasawa, Koichi (8), 1968 (Box 22, Folder 548)
  - Moise, Edwin Evariste (3), 1960 (Box 22, Folder 549)
  - Molina, Edward C. (3), 1959 (Box 22, Folder 549)
  - Montgomery, Deane (9), 1955, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 550)
  - Montgomery, Deane (2), 1957 (Box 66B, Folder 83)
  - Mood, Alexander McFarlane (6), 1951, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 551)
  - Mood, Alexander McFarlane (1), 1962 (Box 66B, Folder 83)
  - Moore, Jan (6), 1964 (Box 22, Folder 552)
  - Morales, Manuel Frank (10), 1955-1957 (Box 23, Folder 553)
  - Morales, Manuel Frank (2), 1957 (Box 66B, Folder 84)
  - Morawetz, Herbert (3), 1971 (Box 23, Folder 554)
  - Morganbesser, Sidney (7), 1965 (Box 23, Folder 554)
  - Morgenstern, Oskar (2), 1953 (Box 23, Folder 555)
  - Moriguti, Sigeiti (2), 1961 (Box 23, Folder 555)
  - Morlat, Georges (20), 1952-1955, 1959-1960 (Box 23, Folder 556)
  - Morlat, Georges (24), 1963, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 557)
  - Morlat, Georges (23), 1968, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 558)
  - Morlat, Georges (3), 1966, 1970 (Box 66B, Folder 84)
  - Moses, Lincoln E. (2), 1960 (Box 23, Folder 559)
  - Mosteller, Frederick (36), 1946-1949, 1951, 1953-1954, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 560)
  - Mosteller, Frederick (18), 1957-1959 (Box 23, Folder 561)
  - Mosteller, Frederick (50), 1960-1964, 1966-1967, 1969-1971, undated (Box 23, Folder 562)
  - Mosteller, Frederick (1), 1964 (Box 66B, Folder 85)
  - Mowrer, Orval Hobart (10), 1959-1960 (Box 23, Folder 563)
  - Moy, Shu Teh (5), 1956, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 564)
  - Murphy, Allan Hunt (9), 1964, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 564)
  - Myers, Allison (5), 1946, 1955, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 565)
  - Myslivec, Vaclav (7), 1969-1971 (Box 23, Folder 565)
  - N (6), 1964, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 566)
  - Nagel, Ernest (1), 1962 (Box 23, Folder 567)
  - Narayana, T. V. (31), 1959-1963 (Box 23, Folder 568)
  - National Academy of Sciences, National Research Council (29), 1951-1952, 1954, 1957, 1959-1961, 1963, 1965-1966, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 569)
  - National Register of Scientific and Technical Personnel (7), 1956, 1960, 1964, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 570)
  - National Science Foundation (11), 1958, 1963-1964, 1971, undated (Box 23, Folder 571)
  - National Science Foundation (5), 1955-1956, 1965-1966, 1969-1970 (Box 66B, Folder 85)
  - Naval Medical Research Institute (10), 1955 (Box 23, Folder 572)
  - Neff, John David (10), 1950, 1957, 1961, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 573)
  - Nesbitt, Cecil James (40), 1959-1960, undated (Box 23, Folder 574)
  - New York University (5), 1943, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 575)
  - Newman, Daisy (3), 1964-1965 (Box 23, Folder 576)
  - Newman, Peter (5), 1965 (Box 23, Folder 576)
  - Neyman, Jerzy (19), 1948-1950, 1955, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 577)
  - Neyman, Jerzy (15), 1960-1961, 1965, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 578)
  - Nichols, Russell (7), 1954-1956, l962 (Box 23, Folder 579)
  - Niiniluoto, Ilkka (3), 1971 (Box 23, Folder 580)
  - Norman, Frank (2), 1963 (Box 24, Folder 581)
  - North Carolina State College, Institute of of Statistics (9), 1960, 1962-1963 (Box 24, Folder 582)
  - Norton, John H. (2), 1962 (Box 24, Folder 582)
  - Novick, Aaron (2), 1965 (Box 24, Folder 583)
  - Novick, Melvin R. (9), 1962-1963, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 584)
  - O (13), 1953, 1955, 1958, 1961, 1966, 1969, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 585)
  - Oak Ridge National Laboratory (1), 1941 (Box 24, Folder 586)
  - Odorant Exhibit
    - Arctander, Steffin (5), 1967, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 587)
    - Belisle, Phyllis S. (1), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 587)
    - Canadian Consulate General (4), 1971 (Box 24, Folder 587)
    - Archer Daniels Co. (1), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 588)
    - Gerard J. Danco International Corp. (1), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 588)
    - Dodge and Olcott Inc. (1), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 588)
    - Faberge (2), 1970 (Box 24, Folder 589)
    - Flavor and Extract Manufacturers' Association (2), 1970 (Box 24, Folder 589)
    - Forsyth, Louise (5), 1962, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 590)
    - Fuller, George (1), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 590)
    - Givaudan Corporation (2), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 590)
    - Harrison, John A. (1), 1969 (Box 24, Folder 590)
    - Idyll, C.P. (4), 1967, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 591)
    - International Flavors and Fragrances Inc. (11), 1967, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 591)
    - Kommandor Chr. Christensens Hvalfangstmuseum (1), 1962 (Box 24, Folder 592)
    - George Lueders and Co., Inc. (2), 1970 (Box 24, Folder 592)
    - J. Manheimer Inc. (13), 1967-1971 (Box 24, Folder 593)
    - Nantucket Historical Association (2), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 593)
    - Old Dartmouth Historical Society (5), 1962, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 594)
    - Peabody Museum of Natural History (20), 1967, 1969-1971 (Box 24, Folder 594)
    - Roudnitska, Edmond (2), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 595)
    - Schimmel and Co, Inc. (1), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 595)
    - Thomson, Keith (1) (Box 24, Folder 595)
    - U. S. Food and Drug Administration (2), 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 595)
    - Bibliography and background material (Box 24, Folder 596)
    - notes (Box 24, Folder 597)
    - publicity materials (Box 24, Folder 598)
    - text for labels (Box 24, Folder 599)
    - Office of Naval Research (48), 1955, 1960-1961 (Box 24, Folder 600)
    - Office of Naval Research (23), 1962 (Box 24, Folder 601)
    - Office of Naval Research (32), 1963-1965, 1969, 1971, undated (Box 24, Folder 602)
    - Office of Naval Research, financial materials (Box 24, Folder 603)
    - Ohio State University (1), 1947 (Box 25, Folder 604)
    - Olkin, Ingram (15), 1962, 1969-1971 (Box 25, Folder 605)
    - Olshen, Richard Allen (27), 1963, 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 606)
    - Olshen, Richard Allen (13), 1970-1971, undated (Box 25, Folder 607)
    - Onicescu, Octav (5), 1971 (Box 25, Folder 608)
    - P (29), 1948, 1953-1954, 1958, 1960-1967, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 609)
    - Patil, Ganapati P. (13), 1961-1963, 1966, undated (Box 25, Folder 610-611)
    - Patil, Venkutai H. (16), 1963 April-1965, undated (Box 25, Folder 612)
    - Patrick, C. (4), 1971 (Box 25, Folder 613)
  - Olkin, Ingram (2), 1963 (Box 66B, Folder 86)
  - Olshen, Richard Allen (4), 1962, 1967 (Box 66B, Folder 86)
  - Patil, Ganapati P. (6), 1961, 1963, 1965 (Box 66B, Folder 87)
  - Patil, Venkutai H. (8), 1961-1963 (Box 66B, Folder 87)
  - Pearson, Egon Sharpe (10), 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 614)
  - Pearson, Egon Sharpe (31), 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 615)
  - Perlman, Michael D. (3), 1971 (Box 25, Folder 616)
  - Personnel: miscellaneous notes, 1956, 1966-1967, 1969-1970 (Box 66B, Folder 88)
  - Pfanzagl, J. (5), 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 617)
  - Philosophy of Science (7), 1967 (Box 25, Folder 618)
  - Pike, Malcolm C. (4), 1959 (Box 25, Folder 619)
  - Pillai, Ramanpillai Krishna, 1961-1962 (Box 66B, Folder 88)
  - Pitman, E. J. G. (11), 1957, 1964, 1966, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 620)
  - Pollaczek, Penny (4), 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 621)
  - Polya, George (3), 1954-1955 (Box 25, Folder 621)
  - Popper, Karl R. (4), 1958 (Box 25, Folder 622)
  - Pratt, John W. (73 Sheets), 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 623)
  - Pratt, John W. (100 Sheets), 1960 (Box 25, Folder 624)
  - Pratt, John W. (158 Sheets), 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 625)
  - Pratt, John W. (82 Sheets), 1963-1970, undated (Box 25, Folder 626)
  - Pratt, John W. (23), 1960-1961, 1964 (Box 66B, Folder 89)
  - Press, S. James (3), 1967 (Box 25, Folder 627)
  - Price, Derek John de Solla (4), 1968 (Box 25, Folder 628)
  - Puck, Theodore Thomas (4), 1948 (Box 26, Folder 629)
  - Purcell, Theodore V. (13), 1953 (Box 26, Folder 630)
  - Purdue University (5), 1961, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 631)
  - Puri, Madan L. (2), 1967 (Box 26, Folder 631)
  - Pyke, Ronald (15), 1964 (Box 26, Folder 632)
  - Quade, Edward Schaumberg (6), 1960 (Box 26, Folder 633)
  - Quade, Edward Schaumberg (15), 1961, 1967-1969, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 634)
  - Quine, Willard Van Orman (5), 1951, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 635)
  - R (39), 1948, 1950, 1952, 1955-1956, 1960-1963, 1965-1966, 1969-1971 undated (Box 26, Folder 636)
  - Rader, Trout (11), 1965-1966, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 637)
  - Rader, Trout (9), 1965-1966 (Box 66C, Folder 90)
  - Radner, Roy (16), 1955-1956, 1959, 1963, 1969-1971 (Box 26, Folder 638)
  - Radner, Roy (2), 1957, 1960 (Box 66C, Folder 90)
  - Raiffa, Howard (13), 1962-1963, 1965-1966 (Box 26, Folder 639)
  - Raiffa, Howard (5), 1969 (Box 26, Folder 640)
  - Ramage, John G (6), 1969, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 641)
  - The Rand Corporation (30), 1947-1948, 1950-1956 (Box 26, Folder 642)
  - The Rand Corporation (35), 1957-1959, 1961, 1963-1967, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 643)
  - The Rand Corporation (1), 1948 (Box 66C, Folder 91)
  - The Rand Corporation (agreements, contracts) (20), 1959-1964, 1966-1971 (Box 26, Folder 644)
  - The Rand Corporation (personnel security questionnaires) (3) (Box 26, Folder 645)
  - Rao, C. R. (3), 1962, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 646)
  - Raoult, Jean Pierre (4), 1964-1966 (Box 27, Folder 646)
  - Rasch, George (7), 1952, 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 647)
  - Reed, Lowell Jacob (2), 1945 (Box 27, Folder 648)
  - Reinhardt, Howard Earl (23), 1962-1964 (Box 27, Folder 649)
  - Relles, Daniel Arthur (2), 1967 (Box 27, Folder 650)
  - Relles, Daniel Arthur (1), 1965 (Box 66C, Folder 91)
  - Rescher, Nicholas, undated
    See: box 15, folder 367
  - Richter, Hans (5), 1955 (Box 27, Folder 651)
  - Rinehart and Company, Inc. (1), 1959 (Box 27, Folder 651)
  - Riordan, John (8), 1970 (Box 27, Folder 652)
  - Rios, Sixtos (16), 1953-1955 (Box 27, Folder 653)
  - Roberts, Harry Vivian (9), 1949, 1952, 1956, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 654)
  - Roberts, Harry Vivian (4), 1956, 1961 (Box 66C, Folder 92)
  - Roberts, Harry Vivian ("Statistical Inference and Decision, part 1"), 1960 (Box 27, Folder 655)
  - Roberts, Harry Vivian ("Statistical Inference and Decision, part 2"), 1961 (Box 27, Folder 656)
  - Roberts, Harry Vivian ("Statistical Inference and Decision, part 2"), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 657)
  - Roberts, Harry Vivian (11), 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 658)
  - Roberts, Harry Vivian (15), 1964-1965 (Box 27, Folder 659)
  - Roberts, Harry Vivian (2), 1967 June (Box 27, Folder 660)
  - Roberts, Harry Vivian, 1967 July-1968, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 661)
  - Roberts, Harry Vivian (Wallis and Roberts' Statistics: A New Approach, chapters 1-6) (2), 1972 (Box 28, Folder 662)
  - Roberts, Harry Vivian (Wallis and Roberts' Statistics: A New Approach, chapters 7-12), 1972 (Box 28, Folder 663)
  - Roberts, Harry Vivian (Wallis and Roberts' Statistics: A New Approach, chapters 13-14, 16-19), 1972 (Box 28, Folder 664)
  - Robertson, R. E. (7), 1954-1955 (Box 28, Folder 665)
  - Rochester, University of (15), 1962-1963 (Box 28, Folder 666)
  - Rockafellar, Ralph Tyrrell (6), 1970 (Box 28, Folder 667)
  - Rockoff, Maxine Lieberman (7), 1968, 1971, undated (Box 28, Folder 668)
  - Roettinger, Frank G. (4), 1953, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 669)
  - Rosenblatt-Roth, M. (3), 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder 669)
  - Rosenblatt-Roth, Millu (8), 1968-1969 (Box 66C, Folder 92)
  - Rosenthal, Ethel (3), 1963 (Box 28, Folder 670)
  - Rosett, Richard N. (4), 1963, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 671)
  - Rosin, Robert Fisher (12), 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 672)
  - Royal Statistical Society (6), 1960, 1962, 1966, undated (Box 28, Folder 673)
  - Rozeboom, William W. (6), 1961, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 674)
  - Rubin, Herman (5), 1958, 1960 (Box 66C, Folder 93)
  - Rudkin-Wiley Corporation (6), 1965 (Box 28, Folder 675)
  - Rudy, Norman (5), 1950-1951, undated (Box 28, Folder 676)
  - Rushton, S. (2), 1954 (Box 28, Folder 676)
  - S (57), 1944, 1948, 1955, 1961-1963, 1968-1972 (Box 29, Folder 677)
  - Sacksteder, Richard (8), 1964, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 678)
  - Sadowsky, Melvin D. (4), 1962 (Box 29, Folder 679)
  - Salmon, Wesley C. (22), 1963, 1966-1967, 1969-1971 (Box 29, Folder 680)
  - Salmon, Wesley C. (1), 1963 (Box 66C, Folder 94)
  - Salvemeni, T. (3), 1963 (Box 29, Folder 681)
  - Samuel, Ester (33), 1962-1964 (Box 29, Folder 682)
  - Samuelson, Paul Anthony (28), 1948, 1950-1952 (Box 29, Folder 683)
  - Samuelson, Paul Anthony (13), 1956, 1961-1962, 1968-1969, undated (Box 29, Folder 684)
  - Sansbury, Ralph (8), 1970 (Box 29, Folder 685)
  - Sansbury, Ralph (4), 1970 (Box 66C, Folder 93)
  - Sarason, Harry M. (38), 1963-1968, undated (Box 29, Folder 686)
  - Savage, I. Richard (16), 1950-1954 (Box 29, Folder 687)
  - Savage, I. Richard (33), 1956-1959 (Box 29, Folder 688)
  - Savage, I. Richard (8), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 689)
  - Savage, I. Richard (16), 1961 (Box 29, Folder 690)
  - Savage, I. Richard (31), 1962 (Box 29, Folder 691)
  - Savage, I. Richard (19), 1963 (Box 29, Folder 692)
  - Savage, I. Richard (14), 1964 January-April (Box 29, Folder 693)
  - Savage, I. Richard (23), 1964 May-December (Box 30, Folder 694)
  - Savage, I. Richard (18), 1965 (Box 30, Folder 695)
  - Savage, I. Richard (14), 1966 (Box 30, Folder 696)
  - Savage, I. Richard (29), 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 697)
  - Savage, I. Richard (15), 1969 (Box 30, Folder 698)
  - Savage, I. Richard (11), 1970 (Box 30, Folder 699)
  - Savage, I. Richard (16), 1971, undated (Box 30, Folder 700)
  - Savage, I. Richard (24), 1957-1964 (Box 66C, Folder 95)
  - Savage, I. Richard (20), 1965-1971 (Box 66C, Folder 96)
  - Savage, I. Richard
    - Anderson, Theodore Wilbur, Jr. (1), 1971 (Box 30, Folder 701)
    - Anscombe, Francis John (2), 1971 (Box 30, Folder 701)
    - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences (2), 1971 (Box 30, Folder 702)
    - Ericson, William A. (5), 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 702)
    - Gani, J. (1), 1971 (Box 30, Folder 703)
    - Katti, Shri (1), 1971 (Box 30, Folder 703)
    - Konijn, H. S. (1), 1971 (Box 30, Folder 703)
    - Kruskal, William Henry (8), 1972 (Box 30, Folder 704)
    - Mathematical Reviews (1), 1972 (Box 30, Folder 704)
    - Rao, M. M. (1), 197 (Box 30, Folder 705)
    - Sobol, Milton (1), 1971 (Box 30, Folder 705)
    - Wallis, Wilson Allen (9), 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 706)
    - Wolfowitz, Jack (1), 1971 (Box 30, Folder 706)
    - unidentified (1), 1971 (Box 30, Folder 706)
    - Savage, Jean Strickland (4), 1964, 1968-1969, undated (Box 30, Folder 707)
  - Savage, Jean Strickland
    - letters of condolence (24), 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 708)
    - letters of condolence (27), 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 709)
  - Savage, Leonard Jimmie (4), 1969, 1972 (Box 66C, Folder 97)
  - Savage, Louis (6), 1954, 1967, 1970, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 710)
  - Saxena, K. M. Lal (5), 1964, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 711)
  - Scaglietta, Fausta (5), 1968-1970 (Box 30, Folder 711)
  - Scarf, Herbert E. (2), 1962 (Box 66C, Folder 98)
  - Scheffé, Henry (29), 1952, 1955, 1960-1961, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 712)
  - Schelling, Thomas Crombie (7), 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 713)
  - Schelling, Thomas Crombie (1), 1957 (Box 66C, Folder 99)
  - Schlaifer, Robert (36), 1956-1960, 1962, 1969, undated (Box 30, Folder 714)
  - Schliack, V. (3), 1971 (Box 30, Folder 715)
  - Schoeffler, Sidney (6), 1955-1956 (Box 30, Folder 716)
  - Science (9), 1962, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 717)
  - Scientific American (4), 1967 (Box 30, Folder 718)
  - Scott, E. L. (1), 1970 (Box 30, Folder 719)
  - Scott, Foresman and Company (3), 1966 (Box 30, Folder 720)
  - Seiden, Esther (2), 1967 (Box 30, Folder 720)
  - Selective Service System (2), 1970 (Box 30, Folder 721)
  - Semtei, Roberto (8), 1958, undated (Box 30, Folder 722)
  - Sethi, V. K. (4), 1965 (Box 30, Folder 723)
  - Shaffer, Jerome (7), 1964-1966 (Box 31, Folder 724)
  - Shah, B. K. (10), 1967, 1969, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 725)
  - Shaw, Richard F. (4), 1961, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 726)
  - Shepp, Lawrence Alan (5), 1966 (Box 31, Folder 727)
  - Sheppard, Charles Wilcox (11), 1951-1954 (Box 31, Folder 728)
  - Sheppard, Charles Wilcox (33), 1961-1963, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 729)
  - Sheppard, Charles Wilcox, undated (Box 31, Folder 730)
  - Sherman, Seymour (4), 1951, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 731)
  - Shimony, Abner (16), 1963-1964, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 732)
  - Shuford, Emir H., 1961, 1964, 1966, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 733)
  - Siegel, Sidney, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 734)
  - Siegmund, David (2), 1970 (Box 31, Folder 734)
  - Sims, Christopher A. (5), 1968 (Box 31, Folder 735)
  - Sims, Christopher A. (3), 1969-1970 (Box 66C, Folder 99)
  - Singer, Burton H. (3), 1970-1971 (Box 31, Folder 736)